http://www.ZooScape.com/cgi-bin/maitred/ZooScape/questpolicies/jornada41319764#Privacy

Help
Checkout Now »
0 Items
100% Safe and Private!
Baby
for:
1-844-449-0444
Home Page > Welcome!
Our PoliciesSecurity  |  Privacy  |  Shipping  |  Returns, Exchanges and Refunds  |  Where Is My Order?Copyright  |  Disclaimer  |  Bill of RightsYour Cart  |  Still Need Help? Contact Us!Security - Credit Card SafetyAre You Safe?Yes you are!When you place an order with us, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. This means that no prying eyes will be able to see your personal information while it is in transit to us, because it will be encryted.Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption software is the industry standard - it is the best encryption method available today for confident and secure online commerce transactions.Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
All raw data is kept on a stand-alone computer behind a firewall.
No raw personal data is kept on-line anywhere.Still Too Nervous to Place Your Order On-Line?That's alright! You can also provide us with your order and payment information by telephone, toll-free, at 1-844-449-0444 (856-467-2430).May I Pay by Money Order?Yes! 1. Search and browse through all of our stores for the items you are interested in. When you find an item that you are interested in, click the Buy button to add it to your on-line shopping cart.2. When you have filled your cart with all of the items you wish to purchase, simply print or write down the list of items and totals from your on-line shopping cart.3. Purchase a money order for the total amount due.
(Please make sure the money order is negotiable and valid in Canada!)4. Send your order details, money order and mailing address to:     ZooScape - United States    PO Box 10124    Wilmington, Delaware    United States    19850-0124    ZooScape - Canada    51 Mountainash Road     PO Box 15010     Brampton, Ontario     Canada     L6R 2W6 5. We will ship your order when we receive your money order!Go To Top  |   Your CartYour PrivacyDo We Respect Your Privacy?Yes.At ZooScape.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy.We recognize the amazing leap of faith that you may feel you are taking in placing an order with us, and we will not do anything that may betray your trust in us.
We only use the information we collect about you to process your order and to serve you better. Your information plays an important role in our desire to serve you as best we can - We are not in the business of selling your personal information to anyone else. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.What information do we collect? How do we use it?Unlike many www sites, we do not use cookies.When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our Web sites, new ZooScape.com products and services, and special ZooScape.com offers we think you'll find valuable.
If you would rather not receive this information, just let us know by email.
Make sure to note your preferences for each account or e-mail address you have left with us.Will ZooScape.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?ZooScape.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.In summaryWe are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. If you never want to receive any announcements or special offers from us, just let us know by signing in to your account with your email address and adjusting your Communication Preferences.Your consentBy using our Web sites, you consent to the collection and use of this information by ZooScape.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Tell us what you thinkZooScape.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy.Please send e-mail to Help@ZooScape.comGo To Top  |   Your CartShippingShipping Fee CalculationYour Shipping Fee is calculated as fairly as possible based upon the weight or size of the products you have placed in your shopping cart.
Each product has a weight, and a size determined by length, width and height.In determining the Shipping Weight of a package, the maximum of either the Total Weight or the Minimum Density Weight (MDW) must be used.The MDW is determined to ensure that the shipping fee for lightweight and bulky parcels adequately covers the cost of transportation for the space they occupy. It is calculated by using the following formula: (length X width X height) / 6000.Delivery Time EstimateSuggested delivery times are estimates only and do not constitute a guarantee.Restricted CountriesWe regret that we only accept bank drafts and money orders for the following countries:Bulgaria, Georgia, Indonesia, Malaysia, Moldova, Pakistan, Romania, Russia, Singapore, Slovenia, Sri Lanka, Turkey, and Yugoslavia.Go To Top  |   Your CartReturns, Exchanges and RefundsYour Satisfaction is Guaranteed!If you are unhappy with your purchase for any reason, you may return the unopened and unused product to us for a refund, replacement or credit!Please note the following:Shipping fees are not refundable.For health reasons, we cannot accept the return of hygiene items or intimate personal items.We reserve the right to substitute items of equal or greater value.We cannot guarantee the delivery of parcels outside United States or Canada.We cannot accept the return of damaged goods.We cannot accept returns if there are Customs, Duty or shipping fees owing. These fees must be paid by you in advance before you ship your return to us.There is a restocking charge of 10% of the value of the total order (including taxes and shipping costs).Discrepancies in your order must be reported to us within thirty days from the day you received your order.Returns must be made within thirty days from the day you received your order.Returned parcels requiring an exchange or refund will only be accepted providing that you have received your Return Parcel Code in advance of sending the parcel back to us. To obtain this code you are required to contact customer service toll free within North America at 1-844-449-0444 or email customer service at Help@ZooScape.com. When contacting customer service, please be ready to provide one of our friendly representatives with the following information:Customer name used to place the order (name as it appears on credit card, including any middle initials and/or designations as they are found on the front of the credit card used); Internet receipt number received when the order was approved; Product being returned; Reason for return.Please allow us seven to twenty-one business days, from the date we receive your parcel back at our Canadian Distribution Center, to process your refund. Once your refund has been processed, you will receive an email confirmation of that transaction. If you have paid by means of a check or money order, a check will be issued to you within seven to twenty-one business days from the date your parcel was received at our Canadian Distribution Center.What happens if I change my mind and I would like to cancel my order before it ships?To cancel your order please contact us by phone. Orders cannot be canceled via email. Orders that have already been shipped cannot be cancelled. While we regret having to charge for a cancelled order, some people place orders impulsively and then, shortly after, decide they would like to cancel their order. Because of this, we have had to implement this policy. Please understand that even though your item may not have been shipped, ZooScape.com will incur administration costs, phone calls, paper usage and credit card processing fees. So, in an attempt to offer you the lowest prices possible, we are charging a very reasonable cancellation fee of 10% of the value of the total order (including taxes and shipping costs) placed via credit card.Go To Top  |   Your CartWhere is my Order?Has my order been shipped?We cannot guarantee that all products in your order will ship immediately, since our inventory can change dramatically from one moment to the next. Indeed, a product may be in stock when you place your order, and sold out by the time your order is processed for shipping. If one of your ordered items is out of stock, we will try to wait until all ordered products are in stock before shipping your order.
When your out-of-stock item arrives at our warehouse, we will ship you your entire order.
We cannot guarantee when a temporarily out-of-stock item will arrive at our warehouse, but it is usually within 2-3 business days.When will my order arrive?Typically, all orders are shipped by the next business day.
All orders are shipped by air mail, and usually arrive at North American destinations in 3 - 14 business days. Please note that deliveries outside of North America can take up to 6 weeks.Your order may arrive in separate packages at different times.
If your order is large or contains large or out of stock items, we may elect to ship some items in separate packages.My order should have arrived by now. What should I do?If it has been more than 14 business days since you placed your order, please contact us so we may investigate the status of your order.Go To Top  |   Your CartCopyrightAll content included on all ZooScape.com sites, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons and images, are the property of ZooScape Corporation and protected by Canadian and international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement and assembly) of all content on ZooScape.com sites are the exclusive property of ZooScape Corporation and protected by Canadian and international copyright laws. The content on these sites may be used as a shopping and/or research resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance, of the content on any ZooScape.com site is strictly prohibited.Go To Top  |   Your CartDisclaimerAll ZooScape.com sites are provided by ZooScape.com on an "as is" basis. ZooScape.com makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of any site, the information, content, materials or products, included on any site. To the full extent permissible by applicable law, ZooScape.com disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. ZooScape.com will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this site or our products, including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental punitive and consequential damages.Neither ZooScape Corporation nor any of its directors, employees or representatives will be held liable for any damages arising from the use of any WWW site. This comprehensive limitation of liability applies to all damages, including (without limitation) compensatory, direct, indirect or consequential damages, loss of data, income or profit, loss of or damage to property and claims of third parties. Applicable LawAll ZooScape.com sites are created and controlled by ZooScape Corporation in the Province of Ontario, Canada. As such, the laws of the Province of Ontatrio will govern these disclaimers, terms and conditions, without giving effect to any principles or conflicts of laws. We reserve the right to make changes to our site and these disclaimers, terms and conditions at any time.Our Address - United StatesZooScape LLCPO Box 10124Wilmington, DelawareUnited States19850-0124Our Address - CanadaZooScape Corp.51 Mountainash RoadPO Box 15010Brampton, OntarioCanadaL6R 2W6http://www.ZooScape.comGo To Top  |   Your CartZooScape.com Bill of Rights1.  The ZooScape.com Safe Shopping Guarantee protects you while you shop at ZooScape.com so that you never have to worry about credit card safety.We guarantee that every transaction you make at ZooScape.com will be 100% safe.This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at ZooScape.com.If you prefer, you can always mail, fax or telephone in your order and credit card information.2.  ZooScape.com Updates. As a customer, you may occasionally receive e-mail updates about important functionality changes to the website, new ZooScape.com products and services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. But if you'd rather not receive them, please just let us know by email.3.  Privacy. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We may also use it to tell you about changes in our products and services or about special offers we think you'll find valuable. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. For more details, please read the ZooScape.com Privacy Policy.Go To Top  |   Your CartStill have questions?
Please contact us! 3,646,880 people read our FREE ZooScape Newsletter.Sign up now!We respect your privacy, and you can cancel at any timewith one click.»Name:Email:»  Sign In  |  Shipping  |  Returns  |  Privacy  |  About Us  |  Contact Us  |  1-844-449-0444Copyright  2020  ZooScape.com ®
